Guide to the Erroll Garner Archive, 1942-2010 AIS.2015.09 AIS.2015.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1957-1993; I.
  - General, 1.
    - Correspondence from Jan van Diepenbeek, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence from Sarah Vaughan, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence from George Wein, 1957-2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence from Jann Wenner, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence from Margaret Whiting, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence from Andy Williams, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence from Joe Williams, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence from Mary Lou Williams, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence from Ted Williams, 1969-1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Pitch letters to celebrities, 1962-1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Pitch letters to celebrities, 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Martha Glaser Legal, 2.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; contracts and checks, 1962-1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; correspondence, 1953-1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Contents of these documents include financial statements, receipts, newspaper and magazine excerpts, letters, and court documents all related to Martha Glaser's role as manager to Erroll Garner.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; correspondence, 1956-1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      Contents of these documents include correspondences regarding Garner's bookings, travel arrangements, and unpaid travel expenses, royalties to be paid to Garner/the Garner estate, and the probate records of Martha Glaser.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; Power of Attorney, 1954-1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; banking, 1957-2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; legal cases, 1954-2004 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Contents of these documents include correspondence from Martha Glaser concerning booking and payment for Erroll Garner performances, copyright transfers from Garner to Octave Music Publishing Corp., correspondence regarding the legal use of Garner's work and image after his death, and proofs of postcards honoring Garner produced for the USPS.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; publishing, 1957-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Contents of these documents include telegrams, correspondence, payments, and court documents regarding publishing, royalties, and licensing related to photographs, videos, and music of Erroll Garner and banking documents from the Garner Estate.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; royalty, 1953-2001 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Contents of these documents include correspondence Martha Glaser and others regarding Erroll Garner's contracts, licensing, publishing, royalties from record sales, other payments, and rights to his work and likeness after his death, and scans of record, sleeve and magazine ad excerpts of Garner's record sold in Italy.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; accounting and royalty, 1957-2001 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Contents of these documents include correspondence and various documents regarding audits of royalties paid to Erroll Garner, correspondence regarding legal use of Garner's music in media, foreign licensing, copyright renewals, tax returns, bank statements, and documents regarding the Erroll Garner Scholarship Award.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; litigation, 1951-2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      Contents of these documents include correspondence and documents between Martha Glaser and others regarding legal use of Erroll Garner's music in media, litigation, foreign licensing, publishing, awards granted, transfers of master tapes and other physical media, documents related to the Erroll Garner Memorial Foundation, and correspondence regarding apartment searching for Garner.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; documentary, 1955-1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Contents of these documents include documents and correspondence between Ronald L. Nielsen and Martha Glaser regarding permission for using intellectual property from Erroll Garner for a television documentary about Garner, as well as multiple drafts of scripts.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; music publishing, 1956-1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Contents of these documents include Martha Glaser's correspondence and documents regarding Erroll Garner's posthumous biography, legal cases, settlement checks, use of Garner's likeness and music in media, banking information, copyright issues, and payment to Garner for performances.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; Trust Agreement and Will, 1954-1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      Contents of these documents include Martha Glaser's correspondence and documents regarding copyright disputes after Erroll Garner's death, legal cases regarding agreements and payments, record sale reports, Glaser's role as Garner's fiduciary, Garner's Last Will and Testament, and documents regarding appraisal of Garner's Estate.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; probate, 1959-1982 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      Contents of these documents include Martha Glaser's correspondence and documents regarding royalties, copyright renewals and issues regarding Erroll Garner's work, agreements, payments for legal services, documentation of musical recordings, and an appraisal of Garner's Estate after death.
    - Martha Glaser, Legal; royalty bank accounts, 1956-1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      Contents of these documents include Martha Glaser's correspondence regarding legal matters for Erroll Garner's estate, copyright registration, unauthorized use of Garner's music and likeness, documents regarding payments to Garner and banking information for the Garner Estate.
  - Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser, 3.
    - Telegrams, 1950-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence between Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser, 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence between Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence between Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser, 1966-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence between Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Erroll Garner Correspondence (Peggy, Erroll and Martha), 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Erroll Garner Correspondence, 1956-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Erroll Garner Correspondence, 1951-1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Erroll Garner Correspondence, 1955-1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Erroll Garner Financial, 1951-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Contents of this item include documents and correspondence regarding Erroll Garner's financial history, including taxes, refunds, salary, and miscellaneous transactions
    - Memorial Concert, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Contents of these documents include documents and correspondence regarding the memorial concert after Erroll Garner's death, as well as other events and tributes arranged in memory of Garner, which include pamphlets, an obituary, and magazine and newspaper ads.
    - Martha Glaser Personal; Condolence Letters, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Contents of these documents include correspondence to Martha Glaser and the Erroll Garner family regarding Garner's passing.
    - Erroll Garner Writings, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Erroll Garner Personal, 1951-1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Erroll Garner Personal, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Erroll Garner Personal, 1945-1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Erroll Garner Personal, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Erroll Garner Personal, 1946-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Martha Glaser Correspondence- Garner Family, 1975-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Contents of these documents include documents and correspondence between Martha Glaser and Erroll Garner's family regarding finances, updates about Garner's medical condition, issues of Garner's Estate and passing, and personal correspondence years after Garner's death.
    - Martha Glaser Correspondence- Linton Garner, 1977-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Scopr and Content Notes
      Contents of these documents include documents and correspondence between Martha Glaser and Erroll Garner's eldest brother, Linton Garner regarding Erroll's passing, a tribute by Linton for Erroll, and documents regarding Linton's own passing in 2003.
    - Homewood Cemetery Pittsburgh, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Contents of these documents include documents and correspondence between Martha Glaser and Pittsburgh's Homewood Cemetery regarding Erroll Garner's burial, memorial service, headstone design, and other costs associated with Garner's interment with input from the Garner Estate.
    - Erroll Garner Estate, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Contents of these documents include correspondence between Martha Glaser and Erroll Garner's family before and after his death in 1977 regarding tax information and rights to Garner's property, and documents outlining an inventory of Garner's apartment and appraisals.
    - Erroll Garner Telegraph and Correspondence, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Erroll Garner Telegraph and Correspondence, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Erroll Garner Telegraph and Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Martha Glaser Personal; regarding Erroll's Death and Memorial Service, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Martha Glaser Personal; regarding Erroll's Death and Memorial Service, 1977-1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Martha Glaser Personal; regarding Erroll's Death and Memorial Service, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Publicity, II.
  The Publicity series contains national and international newspaper clippings and magazine articles, full magazines, featuring Garner articles, concert programs, handbills, posters, fliers, correspondence regarding appearances, press releases, fan mail, record company catalogues, press contacts, press books, touring and booking correspondence, plus materials regarding other Glaser clients, such as Tiny Grimes and Bill Farrell.
  - U.S. Materials, 1.
    - "Scanned" Newspapers (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Newspapers, 1951-2002 (Box 5, Folder 2-11)
    - Articles, 1956-2003 (Box 5, Folder 12-18)
    - Articles unrelated to Garner, 1947-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Magazines, 1955-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3-18)
    - Magazines, 1990-2003 (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
    - Album Artwork (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
    - Concert Programs, 1950-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8-14)
    - Posters, 1944-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Handbills, ?-2004 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Carnegie Hall Handbills, 1959-1967 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
    - Town Hall Concert, 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with booking agents; Sol Hurok, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with booking agents; Giesen and Boomer, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with booking agents; Giesen and Boomer, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with booking agents; Shaw Artists, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with booking agents; Gale Agency/Tim Gale, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Record Company Items; Telarc, 1958-2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Record Company Items; Cherry Lane, 1958-2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Record Company Items; MGM, 1958-2004 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - ASCAP Award Items, Pied Piper & others, 1977-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Just Jazz PBS, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Materials, 2.
    - Foreign Press Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1977 (Box 8, Folder 18-23)
    - Foreign Magazines, Spanish, 1962-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Foreign Magazines, Canadian, 1962-1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Magazines, Norwegian, 1962-1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Foreign Magazines, Finnish, 1962-1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Magazines, Netherlands, 1962-1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Foreign Magazines, German, 1962-1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Magazines, Italian, 1962-1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Philips, Netherlands (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Tour Documents (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - English/UK Magazines (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - French Magazines, 1957-1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - French Magazines, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - French Magazines, 1965-1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - French Magazines, 1958-1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Concert Programs, 1958-1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Posters, 1958-1974 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Japanese Magazines (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Garner and Record Company Material, 3.
    - Garner and Columbia Articles, 1956-1962 (Box 9, Folder 14-18)
    - Record Company Catalogs (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Record Company Publicity (Miscellaneous) (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Misty, 1960-1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Non Record Label, Radio/TV, 1955-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
    - Press Contacts, lists, 1965-1998 (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
    - Biographies/Testimonials (Box 10, Folder 10-19)
    - James Doran Book-"The Most Happy Piano" (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Artists, not Garner (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Garner Press Books - Misc. Reviews, 1958-1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Postage Stamp Contract, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Video/Documentary Info; Ken Burns' "Jazz" Doc., 1989-2006 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - African American Publicity, 1981-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Ralph Gleason Letters, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Autographed Concert Program, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Seattle World's Fair/ "One World" Concert, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Garner Tribute Flyers (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Glaser Correspondence - Everest Record Group, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Song Title Lists, 1978-2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Lyrics/Poems about Garner (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Garner/Sony - Concert By The Sea, 1977-1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Receipts, 1947-2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Session Logs, 1956-1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Garner Publicity Tape Reel Lists, 1956-1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Garner Publicity Discographies, 1965-1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Touring Materials, 4.
    - Receipts, Itineraries, Correspondence, Contracts, etc., 1952-1998 (Box 11, Folder 16-29)
    - Receipts, Itineraries, Correspondence, Contracts, etc. (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - Business Correspondence with Booking Agencies, Associated Booking (Box 12, Folder 4-11)
    - Musicians Guild and Unions (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Press Materials, 5.
    - Press Releases, 1950-2000 (Box 12, Folder 13-16)
    - Fan Mail, 1950-2001 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Fan Mail, F. Carter Hoodless, 2003-2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Fan Mail, Martin Doudorff, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Webpage Archive Printouts, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Index cards (people's addresses, lists of interviews Erroll did etc.) (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
  - Awards, 1959-1977; 6.
    - ASCAP Pied Piper Award, on marble base, presented to Erroll Garner for distinguished contributions to American music, September 28, 1977 (Box 12, Item 1)
- Sheet Music, III.
  The Sheet Music series contains written orchestrations, also called lead sheets or band arrangements, which were used by the studio musicians and/or by road musicians. As Garner did not read or write music, he never used these, but his groups did. Orchestrations are different from the handwritten lyrics or music composed by the original composer. Lead sheet arrangements are written by staff arrangers based on music provided by the producer and/or composer, and are then scored for the performing group.
  - Published Multi-Artist Song Folios, 1.
    - Music compilation books (include Erroll Garner songs) (Box 13, Folder 1-12)
    - Music compilation books (include Erroll Garner songs) (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Published Erroll Garner Anthologies, 2.
    - Songbooks and Sheet Music (Box 14, Folder 3-10)
    - Songbooks and Sheet Music (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - Stock Charts and Lead Sheets, 3.
    Note that Sy Johnson did the charts. Approximately Â¾ appear to be original, and the rest are photocopies. Some have annotations.
    - Lyrics and Lyricists (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Martha Glaser's notes on sheet music (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - A Groovy Day (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Afinidad (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Afternoon of an Elf (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - All My Loves Are You (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - All Yours (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Bounce with Me (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Blue Brown and Beige (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Blues Garni (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Blues I Can't Forget (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - By Chance (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Cherchez La Femme (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Cote D'Azure (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Dark Pool (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Don't Talk No Holes in my Clothes (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Dreamstreet (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Dreamy (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Duke for Dinner (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Edna May (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Eldorado (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - El Papa Grande (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Erroll's a Garner (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Erroll's Bounce (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Erroll's Blues (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Erroll's Concerto (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Erroll's Peril (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Erroll's Theme (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Fashion Show Theme (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Feeling Is Believing, Lyric by Linton (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Floating on a Cloud (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Fighting Cocks (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - French Doll (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Garner's Escape (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Gaslight (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Gemini (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - In the Beginning (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - It Gets Better Every Time (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Just Blues (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - La Petite Mambo (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Left Bank Swing (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Lick and a Promise (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Like Home (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Like It Is (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Loose Nuts (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Loot to Boot (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Lotus Blues (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Love is Strangest (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Making Waves (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Mambo 207 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Mambo Carmel (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Mambo Erroll (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Mambo Garner (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Minor with the Trio (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Misty, foreign language versions (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Misty, piano lead sheets (Box 15, Folder 60-61)
    - Mood Island (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Moment's Delight (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Moroccan Mambo (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Movin' Around (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Movin' Blues (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Mucho Gusto (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - My Old Kentucky Home, Arrangement of this song by Erroll (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Nervous Waltz (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Night Wind (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - No More Shadows (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - No More Time (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - One Good Turn (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Other Voices (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Paisley Eyes (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Paris Blues (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Paris Bounce (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Paris Midnight (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Paris Theme (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Part Time Blues (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Passing Through (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Pavanne, Arrangement of this classical piece by Garner (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Relaxin' at Sugar Rays (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Reverie by Debussy, Arrangement of this classical piece by Garner (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Samantha (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Shadows (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Shake It but Don't Break It (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Six PM (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Soliloquy (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Solitaire (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Something Happens (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Steve's Theme (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - That's My Baby (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - That's My Kick (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - The Erroll Garner Blues (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Garner Jump (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - The Happy Apple (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - The I'm Not Supposed to be Blues (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - The Way Back Blues (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - The Quaker (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Theme from A New Kind of Love (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - This Time It's Real (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Tippin' Out with Erroll (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Trio (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Up In Erroll's Room (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Untitled Song (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - When Paris Cries (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - You Just Think You've Been in Love (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - You Turn Me Around (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - 7-11 Jump (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Scores for Orchestra, with Parts, 4.
    - Misty (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 16, Folder 40-44)
    - Dreamy (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 16, Folder 45-49)
    - Passing Through (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - A New Kind of Love (Box 16, Folder 51-54)
    - Afinidad (Box 16, Folder 55-56)
    - Nightwind/ In the Park in Paris (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 16, Folder 57-59)
    - Untitled (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
    - A Gospel Song (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
    - Nightwind (different arrangement) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Paris Waltz and Theme (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - What Time It Was (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Samantha's Theme (Also see o/s Box 23) (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Other Voices (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Solitaire (Also see o/s Box 22) (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Fashion Strip, First version, 3x (Also see o/s Box 23) (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
    - Fashion Strip Blues (Also see o/s Box 21) (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Moment's Delight, 4x (Also see o/s Box 23) (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
    - All Yours (Samantha), 2x (Also see o/s Box 23) (Box 17, Folder 18-20)
    - Dreamy, 2x (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - A New Kind of Love (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - A Gospel Song/One Good Turn (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - "T" (Tea For Two) (Also see o/s Box 22) (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
    - This is Always (Also see o/s Box 22) (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
    - Mimi (Also see o/s Box 23) (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
    - Coffee Song (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
    - Cheek to Cheek (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
    - Lot of Livin' to Do (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
    - I Got Rhythm (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
    - Watermelon Man (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 18, Folder 18-19)
    - Paris Bossa Nova (Also see o/s Box 20) (Box 18, Folder 20-23)
    - In the Park in Paris (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Street Where You Live (Also see o/s Box 23) (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
    - Louise, 2x (Box 19, Folder 5-7)
    - The Very Thought of You, 2x (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
    - Steve's Theme (or Steve's Song), 2x (Also see o/s Box 21) (Box 19, Folder 10-12)
    - It Might As Well Be Spring, 2x (Also see o/s Box 21) (Box 19, Folder 13-16)
    - Black Beauty (Duke Ellington) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Dreamy (Oversize 20, Folder 1)
    - Coffee Song (Oversize 20, Folder 2)
    - Cheek to Cheek (Oversize 20, Folder 3-4)
    - Lot of Living to Do (Oversize 20, Folder 5-6)
    - Misty (Oversize 20, Folder 7-9)
    - Creme De Menthe (Oversize 20, Folder 10)
    - I Got Rhythm (Oversize 20, Folder 11-12)
    - Paris Bossa Nova (Oversize 20, Folder 13-14)
    - Watermelon Man (Oversize 20, Folder 15-16)
    - The Very Thought of You (Oversize 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Spring (Oversize 21, Folder 4-5)
    - Fashion Strip Blues (Oversize 21, Folder 6)
    - Steve's Theme (Oversize 21, Folder 7-8)
    - Louise (Oversize 21, Folder 9)
    - Nightwind (Oversize 22, Folder 1)
    - Solitare (Oversize 22, Folder 2)
    - Tea for Two (Oversize 22, Folder 3-6)
    - This is Always (Oversize 22, Folder 7)
    - Mimi (Oversize 23, Folder 1)
    - Samantha (Oversize 23, Folder 2)
    - Fashion Theme (Oversize 23, Folder 3)
    - Street Where You Live (Oversize 23, Folder 4)
    - Moments Delight (Oversize 23, Folder 5)
    - Untitled (Oversize 23, Folder 6)
- Legal Documentation, IV.
  The Legal Documentation series contains licenses (audio, print, and visual), concert contacts (foreign and domestic), copyright registration forms, financial records, record label contracts, lawsuit depositions, and Erroll Garner Memorial Foundation documents.